<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mapa Viral</string>

    <string name="dialog_wait">Aguarde...</string>
    <string name="dialog_success">Sucesso</string>
    <string name="dialog_sorry">Desculpe</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Mapa Viral</string>
    <string name="title_activity_perfil">Deslocamento de usuário</string>
    <string name="title_activity_deslocamento">Deslocamento de usuário</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sintomas">Minhas informações</string>
    <string name="title_activity_termos">Termos de uso</string>
    <string name="title_activity_estatisticas">Estatísticas</string>
    <string name="location_upload_service">Serviço de atualização de local</string>
    <string name="excluir_informacoes"><u>Excluir meus dados do App</u></string>

    <string name="sobre_texto">O app Mapa Viral foi desenvolvido com o objetivo de suprir informações aos órgãos públicos sobre pessoas que possam apresentar sintomas de doenças virais, como gripes, resfriados e a mais recende: Covid-19.\n\nAjude a compartilhar este App para seus amigos e familiares, em prol de informar mais pessoas sobre as zonas de risco dessas doenças.</string>
    <string name="termos_de_uso_texto">Estes Termos e Condições de Uso (“Termos”) estabelecem as regras de utilização pela pessoa física ou jurídica (“Usuário”) que deseja utilizar o aplicativo, consolidado pelo nome “Mapa Viral”, (“Aplicativo").\n\nAo utilizar o Aplicativo, o Usuário fica ciente e concorda que estará automaticamente aderindo e se submetendo integralmente a estes Termos. Fica desde já estabelecido que o Aplicativo reserva para si o direito de modificar estes Termos, ou ainda modificar ou descontinuar a disponibilização do Aplicativo, a qualquer momento e sem qualquer aviso prévio. Caso o Usuário não concorde com quaisquer alterações a estes Termos ou ao Aplicativo, deverá deixar de fazer uso do Aplicativo. A simples utilização do Aplicativo após alteração/atualização dos Termos e/ou do Aplicativo implicará na aceitação automática pelo Usuário destes Termos.\n\n1. Sobre o aplicativo\n\nO Aplicativo consiste em uma plataforma mobile que visa coletar e disponibilizar informações sobre pessoas que possuem ou não sintomas de doenças virais, permitindo o acompanhamento das zonas de risco e estatísticas sobre os usuários que utilizam o sistema.\n\n2. Disponibilidade do Aplicativo\n\nO Aplicativo envidará seus melhores esforços para que não ocorram interrupções nas conexões do Usuário com a plataforma. Contudo, pela própria natureza da ferramenta e em virtude do emprego das tecnologias atualmente disponíveis, o Aplicativo não pode garantir que não ocorrerão interrupções decorrentes de manutenção no seu sistema, falhas no fornecimento de energia elétrica, falhas nos serviços de telecomunicação, e outras situações de casos fortuitos, força maior, ações de terceiros, ou outros.\n\n3. Propriedade Intelectual\n\nUsuário não adquire, por meio dos presentes Termos de Uso ou da Política de Privacidade, nenhum direito de propriedade intelectual ou outros direitos exclusivos, incluindo patentes, desenhos, marcas, direitos autorais ou direitos sobre informações confidenciais ou segredos de negócio, sobre ou relacionados ao Aplicativo, bem como à base de dados composta por dados de Usuários, os quais são de propriedade exclusiva do Aplicativo.\n\nTodo e qualquer conteúdo disponibilizado na plataforma/aplicativo, bem como toda e qualquer base de dados constituída na plataforma pertencem exclusivamente ao Aplicativo e são protegidos pela lei brasileira, especialmente no que se refere à propriedade intelectual e aos direitos autorais. Na qualidade de exclusivo titular da propriedade intelectual da citada base de dados, o Aplicativo poderá utilizá-la livremente e da forma que melhor atenda seus interesses.\n\nO Aplicativo poderá, a seu exclusivo critério, a qualquer tempo e sem necessidade de comunicação prévia ao Usuário: (i) encerrar, modificar ou suspender, total ou parcialmente, o acesso do Usuário à plataforma/aplicativo, quando referido acesso ou cadastro violar as condições estabelecidas nestes Termos de Uso; (ii) excluir, total ou parcialmente, as informações cadastradas pelo Usuário que não estejam em consonância com as disposições destes Termos de Uso;\n\nPoderá, ainda, o Aplicativo, a seu exclusivo critério, suspender, modificar ou encerrar as atividades da plataforma, sem necessidade de comunicação prévia ao Usuário, salvo nas hipóteses de ato de autoridade competente, caso fortuito ou força maior.\n\n4. Sintomas\n\nPara utilizar o App, faz-se necessário um cadastro inicial, onde o Aplicativo coleta informações sobre os dados sintomáticos do usuário, assim como o número de série do aparelho utilizado ao realizar o cadastro, em prol de registrar essas informações no Banco de Dados do sistema. O número de série do aparelho não será compartilhado com outros Aplicativos ou com terceiros.\n\n5. Coordenadas GPS\n\nPara realizar o mapeamento das Zonas de Risco (regiões onde encontram-se maiores concentrações de usuários com sintomas) serão coletadas as coordenadas geográficas do aparelho do usuário. As coordenadas não serão vinculadas a nenhuma informação pessoal do usuário e não serão compartilhadas com outros Aplicativos ou terceiros.\n\n6. Disposições Finais\n\nCaso qualquer disposição destes Termos for considerada ilegal, nula ou inexequível por qualquer razão, as restantes disposições não serão afetadas e manter-se-ão válidas e aplicáveis na máxima extensão possível.\n\nModificado em: 25/03/2020.</string>
    <string name="license_appintro">Apache License\n\nVersion 2.0, January 2004\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/\n\nTERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION\n\n1. Definitions.\n\n"License" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,\n\nand distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.\n\n"Licensor" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by\n\nthe copyright owner that is granting the License.\n\n"Legal Entity" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all\n\nother entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common\n\ncontrol with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,\n\n"control" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the\n\ndirection or management of such entity, whether by contract or\n\notherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the\n\noutstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.\n\n"You" (or "Your") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity\n\nexercising permissions granted by this License.\n\n"Source" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,\n\nincluding but not limited to software source code, documentation\n\nsource, and configuration files.\n\n"Object" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical\n\ntransformation or translation of a Source form, including but\n\nnot limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,\n\nand conversions to other media types.\n\n"Work" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or\n\nObject form, made available under the License, as indicated by a\n\ncopyright notice that is included in or attached to the work\n\n(an example is provided in the Appendix below).\n\n"Derivative Works" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object\n\nform, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the\n\neditorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications\n\nrepresent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes\n\nof this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain\n\nseparable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,\n\nthe Work and Derivative Works thereof.\n\n"Contribution" shall mean any work of authorship, including\n\nthe original version of the Work and any modifications or additions\n\nto that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally\n\nsubmitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner\n\nor by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of\n\nthe copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, "submitted"\n\nmeans any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent\n\nto the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to\n\ncommunication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,\n\nand issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the\n\nLicensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but\n\nexcluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise\n\ndesignated in writing by the copyright owner as "Not a Contribution."\n\n"Contributor" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity\n\non behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and\n\nsubsequently incorporated within the Work.\n\n2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of\n\nthis License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,\n\nworldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable\n\ncopyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,\n\npublicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the\n\nWork and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.\n\n3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of\n\nthis License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,\n\nworldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable\n\n(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,\n\nuse, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,\n\nwhere such license applies only to those patent claims licensable\n\nby such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their\n\nContribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)\n\nwith the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You\n\ninstitute patent litigation against any entity (including a\n\ncross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work\n\nor a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct\n\nor contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses\n\ngranted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate\n\nas of the date such litigation is filed.\n\n4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the\n\nWork or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without\n\nmodifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You\n\nmeet the following conditions:\n\n(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or\n\nDerivative Works a copy of this License; and\n\n(b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices\n\nstating that You changed the files; and\n\n© You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works\n\nthat You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and\n\nattribution notices from the Source form of the Work,\n\nexcluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of\n\nthe Derivative Works; and\n\n(d) If the Work includes a "NOTICE" text file as part of its\n\ndistribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must\n\ninclude a readable copy of the attribution notices contained\n\nwithin such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not\n\npertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one\n\nof the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed\n\nas part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or\n\ndocumentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,\n\nwithin a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and\n\nwherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents\n\nof the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and\n\ndo not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution\n\nnotices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside\n\nor as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided\n\nthat such additional attribution notices cannot be construed\n\nas modifying the License.\n\nYou may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and\n\nmay provide additional or different license terms and conditions\n\nfor use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or\n\nfor any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,\n\nreproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with\n\nthe conditions stated in this License.\n\n5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,\n\nany Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work\n\nby You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of\n\nthis License, without any additional terms or conditions.\n\nNotwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify\n\nthe terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed\n\nwith Licensor regarding such Contributions.\n\n6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade\n\nnames, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,\n\nexcept as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the\n\norigin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.\n\n7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or\n\nagreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each\n\nContributor provides its Contributions) on an "AS IS" BASIS,\n\nWITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or\n\nimplied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions\n\nof TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A\n\nPARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the\n\nappropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any\n\nrisks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.\n\n8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,\n\nwhether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,\n\nunless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly\n\nnegligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be\n\nliable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,\n\nincidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a\n\nresult of this License or out of the use or inability to use the\n\nWork (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,\n\nwork stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all\n\nother commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor\n\nhas been advised of the possibility of such damages.\n\n9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing\n\nthe Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,\n\nand charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,\n\nor other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this\n\nLicense. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only\n\non Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf\n\nof any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,\n\ndefend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability\n\nincurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason\n\nof your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.\n\nEND OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS\n\nAPPENDIX: How to apply the Apache License to your work.\n\nTo apply the Apache License to your work, attach the following\n\nboilerplate notice, with the fields enclosed by brackets "[]"\n\nreplaced with your own identifying information. (Don\'t include\n\nthe brackets!)  The text should be enclosed in the appropriate\n\ncomment syntax for the file format. We also recommend that a\n\nfile or class name and description of purpose be included on the\n\nsame "printed page" as the copyright notice for easier\n\nidentification within third-party archives.\n\nCopyright [yyyy] [name of copyright owner]\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");\n\nyou may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n\nYou may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software\n\ndistributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,\n\nWITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.\n\nSee the License for the specific language governing permissions and\n\nlimitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="license_androidstorage">Apache License\n\nVersion 2.0, January 2004\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/\n\nTERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION\n\n1. Definitions.\n\n"License" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,\n\nand distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.\n\n"Licensor" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by\n\nthe copyright owner that is granting the License.\n\n"Legal Entity" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all\n\nother entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common\n\ncontrol with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,\n\n"control" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the\n\ndirection or management of such entity, whether by contract or\n\notherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the\n\noutstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.\n\n"You" (or "Your") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity\n\nexercising permissions granted by this License.\n\n"Source" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,\n\nincluding but not limited to software source code, documentation\n\nsource, and configuration files.\n\n"Object" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical\n\ntransformation or translation of a Source form, including but\n\nnot limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,\n\nand conversions to other media types.\n\n"Work" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or\n\nObject form, made available under the License, as indicated by a\n\ncopyright notice that is included in or attached to the work\n\n(an example is provided in the Appendix below).\n\n"Derivative Works" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object\n\nform, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the\n\neditorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications\n\nrepresent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes\n\nof this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain\n\nseparable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,\n\nthe Work and Derivative Works thereof.\n\n"Contribution" shall mean any work of authorship, including\n\nthe original version of the Work and any modifications or additions\n\nto that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally\n\nsubmitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner\n\nor by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of\n\nthe copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, "submitted"\n\nmeans any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent\n\nto the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to\n\ncommunication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,\n\nand issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the\n\nLicensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but\n\nexcluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise\n\ndesignated in writing by the copyright owner as "Not a Contribution."\n\n"Contributor" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity\n\non behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and\n\nsubsequently incorporated within the Work.\n\n2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of\n\nthis License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,\n\nworldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable\n\ncopyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,\n\npublicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the\n\nWork and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.\n\n3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of\n\nthis License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,\n\nworldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable\n\n(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,\n\nuse, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,\n\nwhere such license applies only to those patent claims licensable\n\nby such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their\n\nContribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)\n\nwith the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You\n\ninstitute patent litigation against any entity (including a\n\ncross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work\n\nor a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct\n\nor contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses\n\ngranted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate\n\nas of the date such litigation is filed.\n\n4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the\n\nWork or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without\n\nmodifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You\n\nmeet the following conditions:\n\n(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or\n\nDerivative Works a copy of this License; and\n\n(b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices\n\nstating that You changed the files; and\n\n© You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works\n\nthat You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and\n\nattribution notices from the Source form of the Work,\n\nexcluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of\n\nthe Derivative Works; and\n\n(d) If the Work includes a "NOTICE" text file as part of its\n\ndistribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must\n\ninclude a readable copy of the attribution notices contained\n\nwithin such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not\n\npertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one\n\nof the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed\n\nas part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or\n\ndocumentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,\n\nwithin a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and\n\nwherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents\n\nof the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and\n\ndo not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution\n\nnotices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside\n\nor as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided\n\nthat such additional attribution notices cannot be construed\n\nas modifying the License.\n\nYou may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and\n\nmay provide additional or different license terms and conditions\n\nfor use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or\n\nfor any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,\n\nreproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with\n\nthe conditions stated in this License.\n\n5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,\n\nany Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work\n\nby You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of\n\nthis License, without any additional terms or conditions.\n\nNotwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify\n\nthe terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed\n\nwith Licensor regarding such Contributions.\n\n6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade\n\nnames, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,\n\nexcept as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the\n\norigin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.\n\n7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or\n\nagreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each\n\nContributor provides its Contributions) on an "AS IS" BASIS,\n\nWITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or\n\nimplied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions\n\nof TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A\n\nPARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the\n\nappropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any\n\nrisks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.\n\n8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,\n\nwhether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,\n\nunless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly\n\nnegligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be\n\nliable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,\n\nincidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a\n\nresult of this License or out of the use or inability to use the\n\nWork (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,\n\nwork stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all\n\nother commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor\n\nhas been advised of the possibility of such damages.\n\n9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing\n\nthe Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,\n\nand charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,\n\nor other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this\n\nLicense. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only\n\non Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf\n\nof any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,\n\ndefend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability\n\nincurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason\n\nof your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.\n\nEND OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS\n\nAPPENDIX: How to apply the Apache License to your work.\n\nTo apply the Apache License to your work, attach the following\n\nboilerplate notice, with the fields enclosed by brackets "{}"\n\nreplaced with your own identifying information. (Don\'t include\n\nthe brackets!)  The text should be enclosed in the appropriate\n\ncomment syntax for the file format. We also recommend that a\n\nfile or class name and description of purpose be included on the\n\nsame "printed page" as the copyright notice for easier\n\nidentification within third-party archives.\n\nCopyright {yyyy} {name of copyright owner}\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");\n\nyou may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n\nYou may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software\n\ndistributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,\n\nWITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.\n\nSee the License for the specific language governing permissions and\n\nlimitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="license_materialdialog">Apache License, Version 2.0 Apache License Version 2.0, January 2004 http://www.apache.org/licenses/\n\nTERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION\n\n1. Definitions.\n\n"License" shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction, and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.\n\n"Licensor" shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by the copyright owner that is granting the License.\n\n"Legal Entity" shall mean the union of the acting entity and all other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition, "control" means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.\n\n"You" (or "Your") shall mean an individual or Legal Entity exercising permissions granted by this License.\n\n"Source" form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications, including but not limited to software source code, documentation source, and configuration files.\n\n"Object" form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical transformation or translation of a Source form, including but not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation, and conversions to other media types.\n\n"Work" shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work (an example is provided in the Appendix below).\n\n"Derivative Works" shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of, the Work and Derivative Works thereof.\n\n"Contribution" shall mean any work of authorship, including the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, "submitted" means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems, and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise designated in writing by the copyright owner as "Not a Contribution."\n\n"Contributor" shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and subsequently incorporated within the Work.\n\n2. Grant of Copyright License.\n\nSubject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of, publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.\n\n3. Grant of Patent License.\n\nSubject to the terms and conditions of this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual, worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable (except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made, use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work, where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s) with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You institute patent litigation against any entity (including a cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate as of the date such litigation is filed.\n\n4. Redistribution.\n\nYou may reproduce and distribute copies of the Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You meet the following conditions:\n\nYou must give any other recipients of the Work or Derivative Works a copy of this License; and You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices stating that You changed the files; and You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and attribution notices from the Source form of the Work, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works; and If the Work includes a "NOTICE" text file as part of its distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or, within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed as modifying the License. You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and may provide additional or different license terms and conditions for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use, reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with the conditions stated in this License.\n\n5. Submission of Contributions.\n\nUnless You explicitly state otherwise, any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of this License, without any additional terms or conditions. Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed with Licensor regarding such Contributions.\n\nTrademarks.\n\nThis License does not grant permission to use the trade names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor, except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.\n\n7. Disclaimer of Warranty.\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each Contributor provides its Contributions) on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.\n\n8. Limitation of Liability.\n\nIn no event and under no legal theory, whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise, unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill, work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor has been advised of the possibility of such damages.\n\n9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability.\n\nWhile redistributing the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer, and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity, or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.\n\nEND OF TERMS AND CONDITIONS\n\nAPPENDIX: How to apply the Apache License to your work\n\nTo apply the Apache License to your work, attach the following boilerplate notice, with the fields enclosed by brackets "[]" replaced with your own identifying information. (Don\'t include the brackets!) The text should be enclosed in the appropriate comment syntax for the file format. We also recommend that a file or class name and description of purpose be included on the same "printed page" as the copyright notice for easier identification within third-party archives.\n\nCopyright 2018 Aidan Follestad\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="license_retrofit">Copyright 2013 Square, Inc.\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");\n\nyou may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n\nYou may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software\n\ndistributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,\n\nWITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.\n\nSee the License for the specific language governing permissions and\n\nlimitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="license_mpandroidchart">Copyright 2020 Philipp Jahoda\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");\n\nyou may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\n\nYou may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software\n\ndistributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,\n\nWITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.\n\nSee the License for the specific language governing permissions and\n\nlimitations under the License.</string>
</resources>
